<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Personal Banking</string>
    <string name="interest_ans">The Interest Rates on term deposit of the bank is subject to change from
        time to time and the same is provided on the website of the Bank and also available at every branch</string>
    <string name="minimum_and_maximum_ans">The minimum and maximum tenor for general/Senior citizen is 15 days and 20 years, respectively.</string>

    <string name="security_ans">The security for the loan is a first mortgage of the property
        proposed to be financed with the proceeds of  Home Loans by way of equitable mortgage by
        deposit of title deeds with memorandum of entry. The Bank will also decide the requirement of
        additional security if required for the process of loan application.</string>
    <string name="maximum_home_loan_ans">Home Loans are available maximum up to  10 Cr.</string>
    <string name="loan_eligibility_ans">We will assess your loan eligibility based on your age, qualification,
        income, number of dependents, spouse income, stability and continuity of your occupation,
        assets, liability base and your savings history and based on the value of the property proposed to be purchased.</string>
    
    <string name="services_ans">Balance Enquiry
 Statement Request
 Mini statements
 Cheque-book Request
 Cheque and Cash Deposits
 International usage
 Fabulous discounts and great deals at various establishments</string>
    <string name="rate_of_interest_ans">Interest @ 4% pa is applicable on the Super Savings Account.</string>
    <string name="minimum_balance_ans">You need to maintain an Monthly Average Balance (MAB) of Rs. 5000 in the Super Savings Account for Metro and Urban Branches, Rs. 2500/- for semi urban Branches and Rs. 500/- for Rural Branches.
</string>






    <string name="blanck"></string>
    <string name="minimum_and_maximum">What is the minimum and maximum tenor for which Retail Term Deposit can be kept with Bank?</string>
    <string name="interest">What is the interest rate applicable for Term Deposits?</string>

    <string name="security">What security will I have to provide?</string>
    <string name="maximum_home_loan">What is the maximum Home Loan Amount I can get?</string>
    <string name="loan_eligibility">How will Bank decide my Home Loan Eligibility?</string>

    <string name="services">What are the services that are available ?</string>
    <string name="rate_of_interest">What is the rate of interest applicable on the Super Savings Account?</string>
    <string name="minimum_balance">What is the minimum balance that I need to maintain in the Super Savings Account? </string>
</resources>
